Guide to the Saybrook College, Yale University, Records of the Master
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Saybrook College, Yale University, records of the master
1943-1966
RU 414
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
The records consist of correspondence concerning disciplinary actions and student recommendations of the master of Saybrook College.
Saybrook College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-K-2 (YRG 13-K-2), Records of the Master of Saybrook College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence concerning disciplinary actions and student recommendations of the master of Saybrook College.
Biographical / Historical
The title "Master" for chief executive officers of residential colleges was changed to "Head of College" in April of 2016.
College students; Student housing; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Saybrook College (Yale University); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Student housing; Yale University -- Students
- Correspondence concerning pre-college alumni, disciplinary actions, and student recommendations, circa 1943-1966; Accession 2001-A-011
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Class of 1903, 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1903s, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1906, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1906s, 1951-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Classes of 1922 and 1922s, 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Classes of 1931 and 1931s, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pre-college alumni, general file, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - V-12, letters of inquiry regarding, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - V-12, non graduates, correspondence (including letters of recommendation) mentioned on personal cards, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)